okay Mavis L from Rancho cucamanga
writes Amy why do you talk about your
so much are you scared we don't
believe you have one we get it you're
disgusting I have to say that I have no
idea what that is in reference
to you
know no idea you know you all know I
have
literally never in my life said that
word before so delusional what did you
just say I said you're delusional said
you're I I
said you know you know what anything me
don't know you always think no you know
what I
can't good walk out like you always do
good walk out like you always you know
why I'm not because because you know why
I'm not and what you wrote is very
hurtful I didn't say anything it's very
hartful to meing I didn't say
anything sit back down Amy okay come
back sit down
K Amy Are you seriously saying that
you've never said the word Andy on
my life never never have I ever said
that word on my life on my children's
lives on my children's children's lives
never have I said that word that's
family and you don't do that to family
wait are you saying your is
family she knows what I'm talking about
nobody knows what you're talking about
you know what I'm talking about nobody
knows okay well let's see what
everybody's talking about take a look
close your eyes okay give me your
hand guess where your finger is right
now my my tastes like
nothing cuz I eat for bre
breakfast hope this kid's ready to ton
of stop talking
out of your right now if my
had a voice it would sound like Terry
Gross with just a mouthful of crackers
my character has a can you
not say my puss's magic with a
on it I don't see what's so hard
about just saying vagina let's fix my
garbage are you that girl from the
television who talks about her all
the time
yes kind of seems like you say a
lot Amy thank
you I see why you would think that and I
I want to sinceriously apologize to my
fans if that's what they thought I was
saying but I have grown a lot this has
been a journey with me and God and
everyone at the precinct near my house
and I know what's in my heart and it is
my
okay I mean and I I do I do want
to say this I do want to say this about
Amy okay I know that we have had our
differences and I know that she knows
that I do hate her okay but she also
does say that like she has a good heart
okay and she says she has a good heart
and family is family thank you for
saying that family is family family's
family family's family that's nice that
was kind of you we'll be right back
[Music]
n